Leanne Booden

Norwich NR1 1FW leannebooden@live.co.uk +44 7960 689767

A highly competent, technically minded, analytical thinker with 10 years of extensive experience in the healthcare sector, looking for a new challenge and career direction. My technical knowledge has been solidified by my work as an independent technology repair technician in my spare time, providing multiple troubleshooting services to a wide range of customers. An effective communicator and collaborator, well-practiced in translating customer/user requirements into real-world solutions.

Work Experience

Student Nurse

NHS-Guildford September 2017 to Present

In my final phase of study for my BSc in Mental Health Nursing. Alongside a multitude of specific skills related to nursing, I gained many valuable transferable skills which are applicable in a vast range of environments.

IT Technician

IT Freelancer-Norwich June 2013 to Present

Providing various technological services, mainly focusing around troubleshooting desktop environments on Windows and MacOS, to a wide range of clients with varying budgets, ensuring that every project was delivered on time and to cost, whilst maintaining a high level of customer satisfaction.

Call Handler

Sensée Itd-Norwich May 2023 to September 2023

Member of the call handling team working remotely to provide outstanding service to people in Case Management/Time

emotional distress and vulnerable situations. Focused on maintaining clear records and giving Management

accurate and succinct instructions, to ensure the appropriate response within acceptable timescales.

- Focused on managing complex situations and communicating effectively with the customer.
- De-escalating potential conflict situations and providing support to those in emotional distress and vulnerable situations.
- Recording information accurately and directing the appropriate resource to the customer to ensure the best outcome.

On Call Coordinator

Better Healthcare-Norwich August 2022 to January 2023

Out of hours support to the main office team including scheduling employees, updating carer availability, interviewing candidates for potential roles and general people management duties to

ensure the effective running of 6 different branches simultaneously.

- Ensuring effective running of 6 different branches simultaneously.
- People management and interviewing potential employees.
- Scheduling employees, updating carer availability and managing resources.

Carer Services Advisor

Caring Together-Norwich
May 2021 to September 2021

Advising and supporting unpaid carers to identify any support needs for themselves of the person they were caring for. Working remotely ensured I focused on managing a challenging workload and maintaining professionalism towards the customer.

- Focused on managing complex situations and communicating detailed procedures.
- De-escalating potential conflict situations and providing resolutions.
- Providing accurate information in a timely manner and directing people to the correct source of care.

Education

BSc in Mental Health Nursing

University of Surrey September 2017 to Present

A Level

East Norfolk Sixth Form College September 2010 to June 2012

GCSE

Stalham High School

September 2005 to June 2009

Skills

- · Case load management
- Detailed documentation production
- Independent problem solving
- Response prioritisation
- Technical support
- Server management
- Software troubleshooting
- Desktop support
- Time management
- Conflict management
- Office experience
- · Microsoft Office
- Document management

- Incident response
- Problem management
- Communication skills